Julia Daly / EdTech Professional

julia.m.daly@gmail.com (203) 218-4923 Cambridge, MA

github.com/jdaly04

in linkedin.com/in/julia-daly

juliamdaly.com

INTRO

I am an accomplished EdTech sales and customer service professional with full-stack web development skills. I have a six-year track record of excelling in fast-paced, goal-oriented educational organizations and am looking to apply my unique combination of technical and soft skills to solving problems in the digital learning field.

SKILLS

| Javascript | Node.js |
|------------|------------|
| Bootstrap | HTML5 |
| Ruby | Ember.js |
| Github | CSS3 |
| Rails | MongoDB |
| PostgreSQL | Handlebars |
| SQL | Mongoose |

EXPERIENCE

10/2016 - 01/2017

Web Developer In-Training / General Assembly

- Completed Web Development Immersive course (~600 hours)
- Built four web applications (3 full-stack, 1 front-end) according to strict technical requirements and deadlines
- Implemented debugging strategies to isolate and solve problems
- Developed RESTful APIs as well as SPAs in both team and individual settings

10/2015 - 10/2016

Admissions Producer / General Assembly

- Consistently ranked in the Top 10 company-wide for close rate
- Conducted in-person and phone interviews to screen and accept applicants for full-time and part-time tech-oriented courses
- Consultant for adult students on career trajectory and recommended courses
- Led and presented at weekly information sessions for prospective students

08/2010 - 09/2015

Senior Tour Consultant / EF Educational Tours

- 2013 President's Club Member: #3 in company at 113% over yearly quota
- Provided excellent customer service to 100+ active school accounts
- Increased assigned region's sales 31% from 2012 to 2014
- Marketed and sold international tours to high school administrators, teachers, and students
- Managed all teachers' pre-departure queries and on-tour emergencies
- Co-hosted international training tours for school administrators and educators

EDUCATION

05/2009

Hamilton College / B.A. — Anthropology (Spanish minor)

ABOUT ME

Hobbies: running (I've run the Boston marathon twice and am training for Chicago, 2017), cooking, playing cards. Coffee fiend. Sports lover.